In the documentation for Async Task, we can
scroll down to the section that talks about
protected methods. Here we see that different methods
are called on the UI thread versus on the
background thread. It also contains information on what
order these methods are called in. Relative to the
doInBackground method. For example, onPreExecute gets called on
the UI thread before doInBackground. So with that information
now, we can populate the answers to our quiz. As
we mentioned before, onPreExecute happens on the main thread. And
here you can do any setup work. Then doInBackground happens
on the background thread. While this is running, you can actually
call publishProgress as many times as you want, so that
you can pass information to the UI. So that it
can update an then tell the user that a certain
percentage of the work is done. Each time this is called,.
It triggers onProgressUpdate with some information. Then,
you can show a loading indicator in
your UI that says something's 10% done, 50% done, 100% done. And all this
happens on the main thread. And then, once all of this is complete in
the background thread, then it calls onPostExecute
with the results on the main thread.